<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-07-16T12:27:27+12:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Bunnies</title><link href="/2024/07/16/bunnies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bunnies" /><published>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>/2024/07/16/bunnies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/07/16/bunnies.html"><![CDATA[<p>A bunny is a childs term for a rabbit.
Bunnies are always cute though. I have 13 of them!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bunny is a childs term for a rabbit. Bunnies are always cute though. I have 13 of them!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Firealarm</title><link href="/2024/07/16/firealarm.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Firealarm" /><published>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>/2024/07/16/firealarm</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/07/16/firealarm.html"><![CDATA[<main>
<h3>Pertronic F220</h3>
<p>The Pertronic F220 is a modular, expandable, networkable, intelligent fire panel which displays the exact location of any alarm or other signal activation in a user-friendly format that streamlines the management of critical situations.</p>
<figure><img alt="An F220 in a big cabinet" src="/assets/images/F220.jpg"><figcaption>An F220 in a cabinet.</figcaption>
<p>The F220 uses a 7 inch (180 mm) 800 x 480 pixel colour display to unmistakably identify the panel status. <aside><p>Its cool aye</p></aside>Red status bars and large easy-to-read text descriptors clearly identify the alarm mode. Defect information, device isolation information, pre-alarm conditions, walk test, ancillary and system information all have their own unique coloured display screens, providing comprehensive easy to use information for all users including fire brigade personnel, building managers, and service technicians.</p>
</main>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pertronic F220 The Pertronic F220 is a modular, expandable, networkable, intelligent fire panel which displays the exact location of any alarm or other signal activation in a user-friendly format that streamlines the management of critical situations. An F220 in a cabinet. The F220 uses a 7 inch (180 mm) 800 x 480 pixel colour display to unmistakably identify the panel status. Its cool ayeRed status bars and large easy-to-read text descriptors clearly identify the alarm mode. Defect information, device isolation information, pre-alarm conditions, walk test, ancillary and system information all have their own unique coloured display screens, providing comprehensive easy to use information for all users including fire brigade personnel, building managers, and service technicians.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Suitcasepc</title><link href="/2024/07/16/suitcasepc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suitcasepc" /><published>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>/2024/07/16/suitcasepc</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/07/16/suitcasepc.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="off-grid-comms-box">off grid comms box</h1>
<h2 id="possible-names">Possible names</h2>
<ul>
  <li>OGB1</li>
  <li>the football</li>
  <li>command centre</li>
  <li>Lunchbox</li>
  <li>Whopper</li>
  <li>Field Computer</li>
  <li>001</li>
  <li>homebas’d</li>
  <li>Paradox Box</li>
  <li>Pandoras package</li>
  <li>OFFGRIDD1</li>
  <li>FIELD-ONE</li>
  <li>MCMCC MkI</li>
  <li>CIAB MkI (computer in a box)</li>
  <li>BasedBox</li>
  <li>Battlebox</li>
  <li>Safari 1</li>
  <li>Drop Ship</li>
  <li>blackout</li>
  <li>CommLink1</li>
  <li>RabbitBase MkI</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="features">Features</h2>

<ul>
  <li>powerful mini/sff pc with ryzen 7 or intel core 7 running windows and andys ham radio linux or kali or fedora</li>
  <li>keyboard, mouse or trackpad/ball that can switch between devices</li>
  <li>mega battery 1280Wh+</li>
  <li>multiple SDR receivers - rtl-sdr v3/v4, hackRF, sdrplay, limesdr</li>
  <li>SDR transceiver</li>
  <li>GPS modules for all devices</li>
  <li>standalone router
    <ul>
      <li>connects to WAN via cellular/wifi/ethernet</li>
      <li>ethernet ports and WiFi 6 AP</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>raspberry pi’s
    <ul>
      <li>8gb desktop with touchscreen with nvme hat to swap drives for android and linux</li>
      <li>server to host files and offline wiki/video</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>sinewave inverter</li>
  <li>solar panelcharge controller</li>
  <li>usb charging ports</li>
  <li>speaker system with fm am receiver</li>
  <li>lcd screen for battery and sensor info</li>
  <li>pc case fans for ventilation</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[off grid comms box Possible names OGB1 the football command centre Lunchbox Whopper Field Computer 001 homebas’d Paradox Box Pandoras package OFFGRIDD1 FIELD-ONE MCMCC MkI CIAB MkI (computer in a box) BasedBox Battlebox Safari 1 Drop Ship blackout CommLink1 RabbitBase MkI]]></summary></entry></feed>